pacificcapitalbank.com 2016-10-17

# Privacy Policy - Union Bank

## Privacy Policy

Effective December 1, 2015 

At MUFG Union Bank, N.A., and our affiliates and subsidiaries, our number one priority is our relationship with you. We value the faith you have shown in entrusting us with your financial affairs, and we are committed to protecting any personal information we maintain about you. Establishing an effective Privacy Policy, designed to protect your information and provide you with choices on how you would like your information managed, is an important part of our relationship with you. 

## Privacy Notice

Our Privacy Notice explains the type of information we may collect from our customers, the situations in which we may share information about them, and what they can do to limit the sharing of information. 

####   
Special Notice for California Residents

Please click here to see the California Privacy Notice.

## Online Privacy Practices

Effective January, 2016 

MUFG Union Bank, N.A., and our affiliates and subsidiaries value your trust and respect your expectation of privacy. As such, we are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of your personal financial information. 

To review our Privacy Policy, which is incorporated into this document by reference, please click here. California residents’ Important Privacy Choices can be found here. 

This document outlines our privacy practices for visitors to our websites, regardless of the application used to establish the link, as well as for consumers who apply for or obtain services from us, such as loans, deposits, investments, insurance, or a safe deposit box. These practices apply to our family of companies, including MUFG Union Bank, N.A., UnionBanc Investment Services LLC, and HighMark Capital Management, Inc., among others. 

**What Information We May Collect**

**Visitors to Our Website.** As a visitor to our website, you remain anonymous unless you register for a service or otherwise choose to disclose your identity to us, for example, logging into Online Banking. Although we do not collect personal information that identifies people who simply visit our site, we may collect certain limited information about our visitors, such as their IP address (a numeric address assigned automatically to computers and mobile devices when they access the Internet). 

**Customers.** We collect your personal information, for example, when you open an account or apply for a loan; use online banking or enroll in a service; enter into an investing relationship or purchase a mutual fund; and use one of our other financial products or services. We also may receive information about you from information services and consumer reporting agencies. 

For consumers who apply for financial services from us, the types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include, for example, Social Security number and other personal information; financial history and transactions, account balances, and payment history; and consumer report information and asset and investment experience. 

**How We May Share Our Customers' Information**

We may share our customers’ personal information for our everyday business purposes—such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus. We may share our customers’ personal information for our marketing purposes; for joint marketing with other financial companies; for our affiliates’ everyday business purposes; and for our affiliates to market to you. 

You may exercise choices about some sharing of your personal and financial information with Union Bank and our Affiliates (the family of financial companies related by common ownership or control with Union Bank Companies, which include, but are not limited to, Bank of Tokyo-Mitsubishi UFJ, Ltd., and Mitsubishi UFJ Financial Group) and with other financial companies. Customers can limit our sharing by calling 1-888-283-6699 (our menu will prompt you through your choice(s)) or for hearing-impaired assistance, dial TDD, then 1-800-826-7345. 

As a Union Bank online banking customer, you may indicate privacy preferences in a secure session in your online account at unionbank.com by logging on to online banking and changing your Affiliate Information Sharing preferences. 

**How We Protect Our Customers' Information**

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings, as well as information access controls; service provider oversight and confidentiality requirements; employee privacy and information security training; and physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. 

**Cookies and Online Tracking**

**Cookies** We may place "cookies" on a computer or other device type to track a visitor's use of our site. A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on your hard drive. It takes up very little room on your system and helps us to customize our site and make its navigation easier for you. You can set your web browser to inform you when cookies are placed on your computer or to prevent them from being placed. However, if you choose to prevent cookies from being placed, some of our web banking functions may not work properly on your computer or mobile device. Unless you register with us for a service (such as our Online Banking service), the cookies do not provide us with any personally identifying information about you, such as your name, address or login information. 

We may use web analytics tools that may use cookies, including but not limited to; Google Analytics, Coremetics, Foresee, DoubleClick’s Dart for Advertisers and Kenshoo, to collect anonymous information about pages visited, links that are clicked, and other information about the use of our website. We use this information in aggregate to better understand site activity, and to improve our products and services. 

For more information about cookies please visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/

**Flash Shared Objects** (also known as "flash cookies"). As part of our ongoing efforts to enhance our online security and protect your information, Union Bank places flash shared objects on our online banking customers' PCs. This action assists you in conducting your online banking transactions. Please be aware that you can remove these flash shared objects. However, doing so may increase the likelihood that you will be prompted for additional forms of authentication during your online sessions. 

**Web Browser 'Do Not Track' Signals.** We do not respond to Web browser 'do not track' signals at this time because we do not allow third parties to collect personally identifiable information of visitors to our website to track their online activities. 

**Third Parties**

**Links to Other Websites.** Our website may feature links to third-party sites that offer goods, services, or information. Some of these sites may appear as "windows within windows" at our site. When you click on one of these links, you will leave our site and will no longer be subject to Union Bank's Privacy Policy and privacy practices. We are not responsible for the information-collection practices of the other sites that you visit, and we urge you to review their privacy policies before you provide them with any personally identifiable information. Third-party sites may collect and use information about you in a way that is different from that of Union Bank. 

**Social Media.** When you engage with Union Bank on our official social media pages, you make certain information from your social media profile, postings, interactions, etc. available to Union Bank and other participants in these platforms. You can control what data you share, and with whom, through the privacy settings on these social media sites. Any information you share or interaction you may have while participating is subject to the privacy policies and terms of use of those sites. Union Bank monitors and archives conversations on and with official Union Bank Social Media. Union Bank monitors and may archive conversations, via Hearsay Social, with bank Mortgage Consultants. 

**Services and Advertisements by Third Parties.** Third parties may offer services from time to time at our website. If you provide these third parties with information, their use of that information will be subject to their privacy policies, if any, and will not be subject to Union Bank's policy. If you accept third-party goods or services advertised at our site, a third party may be able to determine that you have a relationship with us, for example, if the offer was made only through our site. 

We also may use third parties to provide other services on our behalf, such as website analytics, hosting of microsites, or social media moderation services. These third parties are contractually obligated to comply with Union Bank privacy and security standards and are limited in their use of any information collected on our behalf. 

**Children and Policy**

**Protecting Children.** We feel strongly about protecting the privacy of children. As such, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 through our site. 

**Changes**

**Changes to This Information.** We may amend (add to or change) this information from time to time by posting a notice of the change at this site. Your continued use of our site or any online service following notification will constitute your agreement to any changes. 

**How to Reach Us**

If you have any questions about our Practices, please contact us at [privacy@unionbank.com](mailto:privacy@unionbank.com) or write us at:   
MUFG Union Bank, N.A.   
1980 Saturn Street   
Mail Code V03-955   
Monterey Park, CA 91755-7417
